Guide to the National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter (NOW-NYC) Records TAM.106
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: National and Regional NOW, 1966-2008; 1970-2002; 7.94 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 2 oversized flat boxes
  - NOW New York State -- Legislative Programs, 1981, 1983 (Box 126, Folder 9, Box 153, Folder 22)
  - NOW New York State -- Lobby Day (Albany), 1981-1982 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Brooklyn, 1973, 1975, 1978-1981, 2002 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Buffalo, 1983-1984 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Long Island, 1972, 1978-1979, 1983-1984, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Queens, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Rochester, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Staten Island, 1983-1984 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Syracuse, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - NOW New York State -- Local Chapters -- Westchester, undated (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - NOW New York State -- Memorandum, 1979-1985, 2003 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - NOW New York State -- Newsletters, 1980, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - NOW New York State -- NOW-NYS Reporter Newspaper, 2002, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 23, Box 158, Folder 2)
  - NOW New York State -- Political Action Committee, 1985, 1999, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - NOW New York State -- Project Family: Divorce New York Style, 1980 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - NOW New York State -- Summer Conference (Ithaca, NY), 1979 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - NOW New York State -- The Women's Monthly: An Irregular Periodical, 1980 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - NOW New York State -- Women, Power, and Decision-Making Conference, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - NOW New York State -- Women's Share: Economic Equity Conference, 1985 (Box 127, Folder 13-14)
  - Local Chapters, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Local Chapters, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Local Chapters, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Local Chapters, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Local Chapters, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Local Chapters, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Local Chapters, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Local Chapters, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local Chapters, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Local Chapters, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Local Chapters -- Boston, MA, 1981, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Local Chapters -- California, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 16-17)
  - Local Chapters -- California -- Los Angeles, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Local Chapters -- California -- Palo Alto, 1984 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - Local Chapters -- California -- San Francisco, 1986-1987 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Local Chapters -- Chicago, IL, 1981-1982, 1985-1988 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Local Chapters -- Minnesota, 1982, 2002 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Local Chapters -- New Jersey, 1979, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Local Chapters -- New Jersey -- Passaic County, 1983, 1985 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Local Chapters -- New Jersey -- NOW-NJ Newsbreaks Newspaper, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - Local Chapters -- Philadelphia, PA, 1976 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Local Chapters -- Vermont, 1980 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Local Chapters -- Washington, D.C., 1978 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Local Chapters -- Wisconsin, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- About, 1987, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Administrative, 1983, 1991-1992, 1995-1996, 2002-2003 (Box 128, Folder 11-12)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Advertising Campaigns, 1998-2002 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Blank Templates, undated (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1981-1990 (Box 128, Folder 15, Box 129, Folder Unknown)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box 129, Folder 2-7)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1987-1991 (Box 129, Folder 8-12)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 130, Folder 1-4)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Meeting Minutes, 2000-2002, undated (Box 130, Folder 5-8)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Board Member Directory, 1987, 2002 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Bylaws, undated (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Correspondence, 1983, 2001-2002 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Dine and Donate Program, 1986-1987 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Direct Marketing Training Program, 1982-1987 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Divorce and Separation, 1999 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Elizabeth Cady Stanton Awards, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Event Flyers, 1984-1987, 2002 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- The First Women's Speakout Conference, 1986 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- "Had Enough Cheesecake?" Event, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- "If I Were Elected President of the United States in 1988" Essay Contest (Box 130, Folder 18, Box 131, Folder 1-4)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- "Love Your Body Day Bash!", 2008; TW_TAM_106_ER_2
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Memorandum, 1984-1986, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Operating Grant Proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Personnel Policies, undated (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Press Releases, 1982-1987 (Box 131, Folder 8-10, Box 132, Folder 1-4)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Program Evaluation, 1985-1987 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- "Why I Really, Really Really Love the Cosby Show, Positive Images of Women and Men, Boys and Girls" Essay Contest, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 6-9)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Women and Technology, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- The Women's Helpline, 1987 and circa 2002 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Service Fund of NOW-NYC -- Your Rights as a Pregnant Worker, undated (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- 10th Anniversary Equal Opportunity Awards Dinner, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Aid to Afghan Women, 2002 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Arbitration, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Blumberg Law Suit (Maternity Leave), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Equal Rights for Women Campaign, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Child Support Enforcement Watch, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Correspondence, 1975, 1979 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Equal Rights for Women, 1972-1973 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- ERA Impact Clearinghouse, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 8-9)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- A Guide to Your Rights as a Military Wife, 1981 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Legal Resource Kit: Stalking, 1999 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Legal Resource Kit: Violence Against Women, 1999 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Memorandum, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- National Assembly on the Future of the Family, 1979 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - NOW Legal Defense & Education Fund -- Paternity Leave Lawsuit, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Welfare, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Working First, But Working Poor, 2001 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - WomanPower PAC, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Womanpower PAC -- 1984 Presidential Election (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Womanpower PAC -- 1985 Election (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Womanpower PAC -- 2002 New York State Elections (Box 133, Folder 19, Box 134, Folder 1-4)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Bylaws, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Democratic National Convention, 1979-1980 (Box 134, Folder 6-7)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Directories, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Endorsements, 1978, 1982, 1985-1986 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Political Action Committees, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Handwritten Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Meeting Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Memorandum, 1984-1985 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Official PAC Manual, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Political Organizing Manual, undated (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Presidential Contenders, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Press Releases, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Questionnaires, 1985-1986, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Republican National Convention, 1980 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Rules of Operation, 1983, 1993, 2000 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Womanpower PAC -- Stationary, undated (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Action Alerts, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Correspondence, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Endorsements, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Flyers, undated (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Governor George Pataki, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Legislative Updates, 1997, 2000-2001 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- President George W. Bush, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - PAC of NOW-NYC -- Press Releases, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- Series VII: NOW and other Organizations, 1968-2007; 1971-1987; 4.19 Linear Feet in 9 manuscript boxes and an oversized flat box
  This series includes materials from other organizations that either worked directly with NOW-NYC or were affiliated with them. These groups include, but are not limited to: the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), Women Office Workers (WOW), ERAmerica, the National Congress of Neighborhood Women (NCNW), the Women's Funding Coalition (WFC), the National Women's Political Caucus (NWPC), the New York Citizens Committee for Responsible Media (NYCCRM), and the Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC). Materials in this series include informational brochures, correspondence, meeting minutes, press releases, event flyers, memorandum, and fact sheets.
  This series is arranged alphabetically first by subject and then by organization name.
  - Anti-Sexism -- National Men's Organization, undated (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Arts -- Women's Interart Center, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Arts -- Other Groups, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Child Care -- Child Care, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Child Care -- The Day Care Forum, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Child Care -- Other Groups, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Domestic Violence -- Coalition of Battered Women's Advocates, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Domestic Violence -- Human Resources Administration (HRA) Battered Women's Shelter Advisory Board, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Domestic Violence -- National Center on Women and Family Law, 1982-1983 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Domestic Violence -- Sanctuary for Families, 1984-1985 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Education -- Chancellor's Task Force and Sex Equity, 1984, 1993-1994 (Box 136, Folder 11-12)
  - Education -- Other Groups, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Education -- Woman School, 1975 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Education -- The Women's Bureau, U.S. Department of Labor, 1970-1971 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Employment -- American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1979 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Employment -- Area Bar Assistance Region (ABAR) Project, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 16, Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Employment -- Coalition for the Unemployed, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Employment -- Coalition of Labor Union Women, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Employment -- The Committee for Women in Nontraditional Jobs, 1981-1982 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Employment -- Just One Break, Inc. (JOB), 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Employment -- Metropolitan New York Project Equality, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Employment -- National Association of 9 to 5 Working Women, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Employment -- New York City Council Committees on Women, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Employment -- New York City Employment and Training Planning Council, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Employment -- New York State Division of Human Rights, 1977-1979 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Employment -- Other Groups, 1970-1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Employment -- Women's Occupational Health Resource Center, 1979 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Employment -- Women Office Workers (WOW), 1975-1980 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Employment -- The Women's Project for Union Democracy, 2002 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Employment -- Working Women United Institute, undated (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - ERA -- ERAmerica, 1980-1981 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - ERA -- Labor for Equal Rights Now (LERN), 1979 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - ERA -- New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU), circa 1980s (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - ERA -- other groups, 1970-1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - ERA -- Religious Committee for the ERA, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - ERA -- Women for Racial and Economic Equality (WREE), 1985 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Family Relations -- Good Old Lower East Side, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - Feminist Groups -- Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - Feminist Groups -- Congress to Unite Women, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Feminist Groups -- Feminist Development Fund, 1977-1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Groups -- Feminist Forums, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Feminist Groups -- Feminist Invention Group, Inc., 1973-1974 1977 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Groups -- Feminist Organization for Communication, Action, and Service (FOCAS), 1971 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Feminist Groups -- Future Homemakers of America, 1977-1978 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Feminist Groups -- National Black Feminist Organization, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Feminist Groups -- National Congress of Neighborhood Women, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Feminist Groups -- National Congress of Neighborhood Women -- Project Open Doors, 1977-1980 (Box 138, Folder 6-7)
  - Feminist Groups -- N.D.C. Women's Rights Committee, undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Feminist Groups -- New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1982-1985 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Feminist Groups -- New York City Feminist Community Coalition, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Feminist Groups -- New York City Women's Lobby, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Groups -- New York Radical Feminists, 1971, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11, Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Groups -- New York State Assembly Task Force on Women's Issues, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Feminist Groups -- Other Groups, 1971-1982, 1987, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 12, Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Feminist Groups -- Redstockings of the Women's Liberation Movement, 1978 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Feminist Groups -- Sagaris, 1974-1975 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Feminist Groups -- Third World Women's Caucus, undated (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Feminist Groups -- United Women's Contingent, undated (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Feminist Groups -- Veteran Feminists of America, 2000, 2002 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Feminist Groups -- Womanspace, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Action Alliance, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Advisors of New York City, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Advocacy Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women Against Pornography, 1982-1983 (Box 139, Folder 13-14)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Bar Association, undated (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's City Club of New York, 2002 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Funding Coalition, 1980-1982, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 17-19)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Graphics Collective, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Liberation Center, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Groups -- Women's Strike Coalition, undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Health -- Other Groups, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Herstory -- Other Groups, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Housing -- Women's Housing Coalition, 1989 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Human Trafficking -- New York State Anti-Trafficking Coalition, 2006-2007; TW_TAM_106_ER_3
  - Image of Women -- Other Groups, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Image of Women -- Women in Media Alliance, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - International Feminism -- International Women's Movement, 1971-1976, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 17, Box 140, Folder 4)
  - International Feminism -- International Women's Year, 1975-1976 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - International Feminism -- U.S. Government International Visitor Program, 1979-1982 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - International Feminism -- Various, 1978-1983 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Legislation and Politics -- The City Project and Alterbudget, 1986-1987 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Legislation and Politics -- Coalition for a Decent U.S.A., 1981 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Legislation and Politics -- Everywoman's Coalition, 1985 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Legislation and Politics -- Feminist Party, 1972 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Legislation and Politics -- The League of Women Voters, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Legislation and Politics -- The League of Women Voters of the City of New York, 1989, 1991 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Legislation and Politics -- Manhattan's Women's Political Caucus, undated (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Legislation and Politics -- National Women's Political Caucus, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Legislation and Politics -- National Women's Political Caucus, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Legislation and Politics -- National Women's Political Caucus, 1971-1975, 1984 (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
  - Legislation and Politics -- New York Citizens Committee for Responsible Media (NYCCRM), 1977-1984 (Box 141, Folder 3-7, Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Legislation and Politics -- New York City Women's Lobby, 1978 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Legislation and Politics -- New York Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Legislation and Politics -- New York Radical Feminists, 1971 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Legislation and Politics -- New York State Assembly Legislative Task Force on Women's Issues, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Legislation and Politics -- Other Groups, 1967-1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Legislation and Politics -- People's Anti-War Mobilization, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Lesbian Rights -- Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1985-1986 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Lesbian Rights -- Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Lesbian Rights -- Lesbian and Gay Community Service Center, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Lesbian Rights -- Other Groups, 1970-1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Marriage and Divorce -- Displaced Homemakers Network, Inc., undated (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Marriage and Divorce -- Other Groups, 1971-1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers -- The Alliance Link, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers -- Chelsea Clinton News, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - Newspapers -- The Feminist Times, 1984 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - Newspapers -- The Feminist Women's Health Center Report, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - Newspapers -- International Women's Year Bulletin, 1974-1976 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers -- Manhattan Tribune, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 28)
  - Newspapers -- Metropolitan Almanac: Women's Lib NOW Supplement, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 29)
  - Newspapers -- Nassau Herald's Sisterhood Week, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 30-31)
  - Newspapers -- New Youth Connections NYC, 1990 (Box 153, Folder 32)
  - Newspapers -- Other Groups, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Newspapers -- Speak Out, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers -- The Spokeswoman, 1972-1975 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Older Women's Issues -- 40 Plus Club, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Older Women's Issues -- American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Older Women's Issues -- National Action Forum for Older Women, 1978 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Older Women's Issues -- National Council on Aging (ACOA), 1986 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Older Women's Issues -- New York State Coalition of the Concerned for Older Americans (COCOA), 1983 (Box 142, Folder 15-16)
  - Older Women's Issues -- Older Women's League, 1986-1987 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Older Women's Issues -- Older Women's Liberation (OWL), 1972 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Older Women's Issues -- Other Groups, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Older Women's Issues -- Senior Action in a Gay Environment (SAGE), 1987 (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Prostitution -- Other Groups, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Rape Prevention -- Brooklyn's Women AntiRape Exchange (BWARE), 1985 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Rape Prevention -- Inez Garcia Defense Committee, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Rape Prevention -- New York City Advisory Take Force on Rape, 1981-1985 (Box 143, Folder 2-3)
  - Rape Prevention -- New York City Mayors' Office to Combat Domestic Violence, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Rape Prevention -- New York Rape Coalition, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Rape Prevention -- New York Women Against Rape, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Rape Prevention -- other groups, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Rape Prevention -- The Street Harassment Project, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Rape Prevention -- Women Organized Against Rape (WOAR), 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 29, Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Rape Prevention--Women's Anti-Rape Coalition, 1973, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 30, Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive Rights -- American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) Women's Rights Project, 1974 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Committee to End Sterilization Abuse (CESA), 1978 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive Rights -- International Tribunal on Abortion, Contraception, and Forced Sterilization, 1972 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Rights -- National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL), 1971-1976 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Reproductive Rights -- New York Woman's National Abortion Action Coalition, undated (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Reproductive Rights -- New Yorkers for Abortion Law Repeal, 1972 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Other Groups, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1971-1973 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Women's National Abortion Coalition, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Women's Strike Coalition, undated (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Sports -- Other Groups, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Series VIII: Photographs, Negatives, and Slides, 1967-2011; 1984-1989, 2002; 6.96 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 4 manuscript boxes, a flat box, and 2 oversized flat boxes